Guide to the Yale School of Drama Audio-Visual Recordings
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Audiorecordings of performances, 1968-1990; Accession 2008-A-112
  - Intermezzo, 1988-1989; 2 (Box 221–222)
  - Interrogating the Nude, 1988-1989; 2 (Box 223–224)
  - In the Clap Shack, 1972-1973; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 225–227)
    - Use copy for boxes 225-227, 2 (Box 225U–226U)
  - In the Jungle of Cities, 1974-1975; 7 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 228–234)
    - Use copy for boxes 228-234, 4 (Box 228U–231U)
  - Ivanov, 1976-1977; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 235–238)
    - Use copy for boxes 235-238, 2 (Box 235U–236U)
  - Ivona, Princess of Burgundia, 1971-1972; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 239–242)
    - Use copy for boxes 239-242, 2 (Box 239U–240U)
  - Jacques Brel, 1979 January; 6 (Box 243–248)
    General
    Performance ran from December 29-January 13, 1979, University Theatre. Directed by Steve Lawson; Music Direction and Arrangements – Rusty Magee; Choreography – Wesley Fata; Sets – Randy Drake; Costumes – Rita Ryack; Lighting – William M. Armstrong. Cast: Caris Corfman, Warren Manzi, Nancy Mayans, Dave K. Miller, H.S. Murphy, Elizabeth Norment, David Prittie.
    - Duplicating Masters
    - Use copies, 4 (Box 243U2, Box 244U2, Box 245U2, Box 246U2)
    - Use copy for boxes 243-248, 2 (Box 243U1, Box 244U1)
  - Joe Turner, 1985-1986; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 249–250)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 249U–250U)
  - Julius Caesar, 1976-1977; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 251–253)
    - Use copy for boxes 251-253, 2 (Box 251U–252U)
  - Kiss of the Spider Woman, 1988-1989; 2 (Box 254–255)
  - A Lesson from Aloes, 1979-1980; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 11–14)
    - Use copy for boxes 11-14, 2 (Box 11U–12U)
  - Life is a Dream, 1971-1972; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 256–260)
    - Use copy for boxes 256-260, 3 (Box 256U–258U)
  - Little Eyolf, 1985-1986; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 262–263)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 262U–263U)
  - Long Day's Journey Into Night, 1981-1982; 3 (Box 264–266)
  - Lorenzaccio, 1984-1985; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 267–269)
    - Use copy for boxes 267-269, 2 (Box 267U–268U)
  - Lower Depths, 1982-1983; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 270–273)
    - Use copy for boxes 270-273, 2 (Box 270U–271U)
  - Lulu, 1974-1975; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 274–276)
    - Use copy for boxes 274-276, 2 (Box 274U–275U)
  - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, 1983-1984; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 277–280)
    - Use copy for boxes 277-280, 2 (Box 277U–278U)
  - Macbett, 1972-1973; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 281–284)
    - Use copy for boxes 281-284, 2 (Box 281U–282U)
  - Mad Dog Blues, 1977-1978; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 285–286)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 285U–286U)
  - Mahagonny, 1978-1979; 6 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 287–292)
    - Use copy for boxes 287-292, 2 (Box 287U–288U)
  - Major Barbara, 1972-1973; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 293–296)
    - Use copy for boxes 293-296, 2 (Box 293U–294U)
  - Major Barbara, 1983-1984; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 297–300)
    - Use copy for boxes 297-300, 2 (Box 297U–298U)
  - Man is Man, 1977-1978; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 301–305)
    - Use copy for boxes 301-305, 3 (Box 301U–303U)
  - Marriage of Bette and Boo, 1972-1973; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 306–307)
    - Use copy for boxes 306-307, audiocassette (Box 306U)
  - Master Harold and the Boys, 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 308–309)
    - Use copy for boxes 308-309, audiocassette (Box 308U)
  - Measure for Measure, 1979-1980; 6 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 310–315)
    - Use copy for boxes 301-315, 3 (Box 310U–312U)
  - Medea, 1987-1988; 2 (Box 316–317)
  - Melons, 1987-1988; 2 (Box 318–319)
  - Midsummer Night's Dream, 1974-1975; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 320–323)
    - Use copy for boxes 320-323, 2 (Box 320U–321U)
  - Midsummer Night's Dream, 7 audiotapes (reel-to-reel), 1975-1976 (Box 324–330)
    - Use copy for boxes 324-330, 3 (Box 324U–326U)
  - The Mirror, 1972-1973; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 545–547)
    - Use copy for boxes 545-547, 2 (Box 545U–546U)
  - The Miser, 1987-1988; 2 (Box 548–549)
  - Mississippi Nude, 1989-1990; 2 (Box 331–332)
  - Mistaken Identities: Guess Work, 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel), 1978-1979 (Box 333–335)
    - Use copy for boxes 333-335, 2 (Box 333U–334U)
  - Mistaken Identities: Identity Crisis, 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 336–337)
  - Moon Over Miami, 1988-1989; 2 (Box 338–339)
  - The My House Play, 1987-1988; 2 (Box 550–551)
  - Narrow Road to the Deep North, 1975-1976; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 340–343)
    - Use copy for boxes 340-343, 2 (Box 340U–341U)
  - Neddy, 1987-1988; audiocassette (Box 344)
  - Night is Mother to the Day, 1983-1984; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 345–349)
    - Use copy for boxes 345-349, 3 (Box 345U–347U)
  - The Overcoat, 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 552–554)
    - Use copy for boxes 552-554, 2 (Box 552U–553U)
  - Pas De Deux, 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 350–351)
    - Use copy for boxes 350-351, audiocassette (Box 350U)
  - Passage, audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 352)
    - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 352U)
  - The Pelican, 1978-1979; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 555–558)
    - Use copy for boxes 555-558, 2 (Box 555U–556U)
  - Pericles, 1983-1984; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 353–354)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 353U–354U)
  - Pericles, 1988; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 355–356)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 355U–356U)
  - Phaedra, 1978-1979; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 357–361)
    - Use copy for boxes 357-361, 4 (Box 357U–360U)
  - The Philanderer, 1982-1983; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 559–561)
    - Use copy for boxes 559-561, audiocassette (Box 559U)
  - Pillars of Society, 1981-1982; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 362–366)
    - Use copy for boxes 362-366, 2 (Box 362U–363U)
  - Platonov, 1984-1985; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 367–370)
    - Use copy for boxes 367-370, 2 (Box 367U–368U)
  - Playboy of the West Indies, 1988-1989; 2 (Box 371–372)
  - The Possessed, 1974-1975; 6 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 562–567)
    - Use copy for boxes 562-567, 3 (Box 562U–564U)
  - Puntila, 1976-1977; 6 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 373–378)
    - Use copy for boxes 373-378, 3 (Box 373U–375U)
  - A Raisen* in the Sund, 1983-1984; 3 (Box 15–17)
  - A Raisin in the Sun, 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 18–22)
  - The Resurrection of Lady Lester, 1980-1981; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 568–572)
    - Use copy for boxes 568-572, 3 (Box 568U–570U)
  - Reunion and Dark Pony, 1977-1978; audiocassette (Box 379)
  - Revenger's Tragedy, 1970-1971; 3 (Box 380–382)
  - The Revenger's Tragedy, 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 573–577)
  - The Ride Across Lake Constance, 1977-1978; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 578–581)
    - Use copy for boxes 578-581, 2 (Box 578U–579U)
  - Rip Van Winkle, 1981-1982; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 383–386)
    - Use copy for boxes 383-386, 2 (Box 383U–384U)
  - Rise and Fall of Mahagonney, 1973-1974; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 387–390)
    - Use copy for boxes 387-390, 2 (Box 387U–388U)
  - Road to Mecca, 1983-1984; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 391–394)
    - Use copy, 4 (Box 391U–394U)
  - Rococo, 1980-1981; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 395–398)
    - Use copy for boxes 395-398, 2 (Box 395U–396U)
  - Room Nerves, 1970-1971; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 400–401)
    - Use copy for boxes 400-401, audiocassette (Box 400U)
  - Rosmerholm, 1970-1971; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 402–406)
    - Use copy for boxes 402-406, 2 (Box 402U–403U)
  - Rum and Coke, 1984-1985; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 407–408)
    - Use copy for boxes 407-408, audiocassette (Box 407U)
  - St. Carmen of the Main, 1988-1989; audiocassette (Box 431)
  - Sally and Marsha, 1980-1981; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 409–413)
    - Use copy for boxes 409-413, 2 (Box 409U–410U)
  - Schlemiel the First, 1973-1974; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 414–417)
    - Use copy for boxes 414-417, 2 (Box 414U–415U)
  - The Sea Gull, 1976-1977; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 582–586)
    - Use copy for boxes 582-586, 3 (Box 582U–584U)
  - The Sea Gull, 1978-1979; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 587–590)
    - Use copy for boxes 587-590, 2 (Box 587U–588U)
  - Sganarelle, 1977-1978; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 418–421)
    - Use copy for boxes 418-421, 2 (Box 418U–419U)
  - Shaft of Love, 1974-1975; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 422–425)
    - Use copy for boxes 422-425, 2 (Box 422U–423U)
  - Shearwater, 1972-1973; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 426–427)
    - Use copy for boxes 426-427, audiocassette (Box 426U)
  - Spring Awakening, 1981-1982; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 428–430)
    - Use copy for boxes 428-430, 2 (Box 428U–429U)
  - Starting Monday, 2 (Box 736–737)
  - Steps, 1970-1971; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 432–433, Box 732)
    - Use copy for boxes432-433 and 732, 2 audiocassettes (Box 432U–433U)
  - Stitchers, 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 434–435)
  - The Suicide, 1980-1981; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 591–595)
    - Use copy for boxes 591-595, 3 (Box 591U–593U)
  - The Suicide, 1985-1986; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 596–597)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 596U–597U)
  - Suicide in B Flat, 1976-1977; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 436–438)
    - Use copy for boxes 436-438, 2 (Box 436U–437U)
  - The Sweet Life, 1983-1984; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 598–601)
    - Use copy for boxes 598-601, 2 (Box 598U–599U)
  - Tales from the Vienna Woods, 1978-1979; 8 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 439–446)
    - Use copy for boxes 439-446, 3 (Box 439U–441U)
  - Talley's Folly, 1984-1985; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 447–448)
  - The Tempest, 1973-1974; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 602–606)
    - Use copy for boxes 602-606, 3 (Box 602U–604U)
  - The Tempest, 1987-1988; 2 (Box 607–608)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 447U–448U)
  - Terra Nova, 1976-1977; 10 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 449–458)
    - Use copy for boxes 449-458, 3 (Box 449U–451U)
  - Terra Nova, 1977-1978; 6 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 459–464)
    - Use copy for boxes 459-464, 2 (Box 459U–460U)
  - Terry by Terry: Terry Won't Talk, 8 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 465–471, Box 733)
  - The Tevening Hours, 1970-1971; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 609)
    - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 609U)
  - They are Dying Out, 1979-1980; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 648–651)
    - Use copy for boxes 648-651, 2 (Box 648U–649U)
  - Three Sisters, 1967-1968; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 652–655)
    - Use copy for boxes 652-655, 2 (Box 652U–653U)
  - Timon of Athens, 1979-1980; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 656–660)
    - Use copy for boxes 656-658, 3 (Box 656U–658U)
  - Tooth of Crime, 1974-1975; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 661–663)
    - Use copy for boxes 661-663, 2 (Box 661U–662U)
  - The Tragical History of Dr. Faustus, 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 610–611)
  - The Trial, 1970-1971; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 612–615)
    - Use copy for boxes 612-615, 2 (Box 612U–613U)
  - The Tubs, 1973-1974; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 616–619)
    - Use copy for boxes 616-619, 2 (Box 616U–617U)
  - Twelfth Night, 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 664–668)
    - Use copy for boxes 664-668, 3 (Box 664U–666U)
  - Twelfth Night, 1978-1979; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 669–673)
    - Use copy for boxes 669-673, 2 (Box 669U–670U)
  - Twelfth Night, 1980-1981; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 674–678)
    - Use copy for boxes 674-678, 3 (Box 674U–676U)
  - Ubu Rex, 1979-1980; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 679–682)
    - Use copy for boxes 679-682, 2 (Box 679U–680U)
  - Uncle Vanya, 1968-1969; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 683–686)
    - Use copy, 4 (Box 683U–686U)
  - Union Boys, 1985-1986; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 687–688)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 687U–688U)
  - Victory, 1974-1975; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 689–692)
    - Use copy for boxes 669-672, 2 (Box 689U–690U)
  - Vietnamization of New Jersey, 1976-1977; 6 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 693–698)
    - Use copy for boxes 673-678, 2 (Box 693U–694U)
  - The Visit, 1975-1976; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 620–622)
    - Use copy for boxes 620-622, 2 (Box 620U–621U)
  - A Walk in the Woods, 1987-1988; 2 (Box 23–24)
  - Walk the Dog, Willie, 1974-1975; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 699–702)
    - Use copy for boxes 679-682, 2 (Box 699U–700U)
  - Wall of Water, 1987-1988; 2 (Box 703–704)
  - Watergate Classics, 1973-1974; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 705–708)
    - Use copy for boxes 705-708, 2 (Box 705U–706U)
  - What the Butler Saw, 1984-1985; 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 709–710)
    - Use copy for boxes 709-710, 2 (Box 709U–710U)
  - The White Devil, 1971-1972; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 623–626)
    - Use copy for boxes 623-626, 2 (Box 623U–624U)
  - White Marriage, 1976-1977; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 711–714)
    - Use copy for boxes 711-714, 2 (Box 711U–712U)
  - The Wild Duck, 1977-1978; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 627–631)
    - Use copy for boxes 627-631, 3 (Box 627U–629U)
  - Wings, 1977-1978; 3 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 715–717)
    - Use copy for boxes 715-717, 2 (Box 715U–716U)
  - The Winter's Tale, 1973-1974; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 632–635)
    - Use copy for boxes 632-635, 2 (Box 632U–633U)
  - The Winter's Tale, 1977-1978; 6 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 636–641)
    - Use copy for boxes 636-641, 3 (Box 636U–638U)
  - The Winter's Tale, 1981-1982; 6 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 642–647)
    - Use copy for boxes 642-647, 3 (Box 642U–644U)
  - Women Beware Women, 1979-1980; 5 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 718–722)
    - Use copy for boxes 718-722, 3 (Box 718U–720U)
  - Yegor Bulychov and Others, 1978-1979; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel) (Box 723–726)
    - Use copy for boxes 723-726, 2 (Box 723U–724U)
- Audiovisual recordings, 1927-1996; Accession 2009-A-067
  - The Blood Knot exerpt from Act I with Athol Fugard and Zakes Mokae, Circa 1985; audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Breuer, Lee, "Epic Theatre," Yale 101 lecture, 1988 February 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 100)
  - Brook, Peter, director, Marat/Sade, videotape (VHS), 1967 (Box 101)
    Production with Patrick Magee and Gleda Jackson, RSC.
  - Chambers, David and Joel Schecter, "Brecht and Political Theatre," Yale 101 lecture, 1988 March 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 102)
  - The Collaborative Effort
    A coproduction of Yale Repertory Theatre and Connecticut Public Radio.
    - Program 1: Prince, Hal and Lloyd Richards, "Directing the New Play [commercially-produced], 1983 January 15; audiocassette (Box 2)
    - Program 2: Gussow, Mel, Edith Oliver, Michael Feingold, and Malcolm Johnson, "Critics on Their Art [commercially-produced], 1983 January 22; audiocassette (Box 3)
    - Program 3: Martin, Elliot, Liz McCann, and Morton Gottleib, "Process on Broadway [commercially-produced], 1983 January 29; audiocassette (Box 4)
    - Program 4: Pendleton, Austin, Fran Kumin, and Jan Miner, "Casting and Performing [commercially-produced], 1983 February 12; audiocassette (Box 5)
    - Program 5: Guare, John, Stuart Browne, and Harry Kondoleon, "Contemporary Playwrights [commercially-produced], 1983 February 19; audiocassette (Box 6)
  - Demonstration of Character Mask, Class of 1988, 1987 March 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 103)
  - Dialect and regional accents
    - Arabic: Iraq and Kuwait, 1995 October; audiocassette (Box 7)
    - Australia, 1995 Spring; audiocassette (Box 8)
    - Bulgaria, 1995 October; audiocassette (Box 9)
    - Canada
      - An 83 year old woman born in Ireland, 1991 September; audiocassette (Box 10)
      - Quebeçois - Montréal, 1988-1989; audiocassette (Box 11)
    - Chinese
      - Hongkong and California, 1995 Spring; audiocassette (Box 12)
      - Taiwan, 1991 September; audiocassette (Box 13)
    - Cuba, 1991 May; audiocassette (Box 14)
    - England
      - Cockney, No unitdate; audiocassette (Box 15)
      - East Anglia (Norwich), No unitdate; audiocassette (Box 80)
      - London, No unitdate; audiocassette (Box 16)
    - Ethiopia, 1991 September 21; audiocassette (Box 17)
    - France
      - Cecile Cohen
        - Tartuffe, Moliere's verses, 36 sentences, 1995 October; audiocassette (Box 18)
        - French verse, sounds in French, 1988; audiocassette (Box 19)
      - Dialect, no unitdate; audiocassette (Box 20)
        - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 20U)
    - Ghana, Circa 1988; audiocassette (Box 17)
    - Greece
      - North, 1991 September 22; audiocassette (Box 21)
      - Merope Vachliotis, 1992 December; audiocassette (Box 22)
    - Ireland
      - Belfast, North Ireland (Karin McCully), 1991 February 21; audiocassette (Box 23)
      - County Wexford, southeast Ireland (George Timmons), 1987 March 3; audiocassette (Box 24)
        - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 24U)
      - Dialect, No unitdate; audiocassette (Box 25)
        - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 25U)
    - Italy, No unitdate; audiocassette (Box 26)
    - Jamaica, 1988 November 8; audiocassette (Box 27)
    - Mexico, 1991 September; audiocassette (Box 28)
    - Puerto Rico, Circa 1990s; audiocassette (Box 29)
    - Russia
      - Vladimir Shpitalnik, 1991 September; audiocassette (Box 28)
      - unidentified speaker, No unitdate; audiocassette (Box 30)
    - Spain, Circa 1990s; audiocassette (Box 29)
    - Slovak-American, 1991 September 29; audiocassette (Box 31)
    - South Africa
      - English-speaking South African (Carol Kaplan), 1988 December 8; audiocassette (Box 32)
        - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 32U)
      - Johannesberg (Mark Gevisser), 1987 November 1; audiocassette (Box 17)
      - Pretoria (Naledi Paul Monama), No unitdate; audiocassette (Box 33)
        Recording includes Athol Fugard glossaries for Statements, The Blood Knot, Hello and Goodbye, and Boesman and Lena.
      - Xhosa-speaking woman (Siphokazi Koyana), 1991 September; audiocassette (Box 109)
        - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 109U)
    - Swahili, Circa 1988; audiocassette (Box 17)
    - Sweden
      - Anne-Margaret Westin, 1991 September 16; audiocassette (Box 21)
      - Swedish-Finnish, Circa 1993; audiocassette (Box 34)
        Recording includes a reading of character names from Ibsen and Strindberg.
      - United States
        - Alabama, Circa 1995; audiocassette (Box 48)
        - Arkansas, Circa 1995; audiocassette (Box 46)
        - Arkansas-Kentucky, Circa 1995; audiocassette (Box 41)
        - Boston (Massachusetts), 1995; audiocassette (Box 42)
        - Brooklyn (New York), 1991 September 24; audiocassette (Box 45)
        - Cajun (Louisiana), Circa 1988; audiocassette (Box 50)
        - Central Pennsylvania, Circa 1993; audiocassette (Box 39)
        - Chicago (Illinois), 1991 February 7; audiocassette (Box 38)
        - Georgia, Circa 1995; 2 (Box 41, Box 48)
        - Harlem (New York), Circa 1980s; audiocassette (Box 37)
        - Jamaica, No unitdate; audiocassette (Box 56)
        - Kentucky, Circa 1988 - Circa 1995; 3 (Box 41, Box 48–49)
        - Long Island (New York), 1993 Sep, 1995; 2 (Box 35, Box 42)
        - Louisiana, circa 1995; audiocassette (Box 41)
        - Maine, 1993 September; audiocassette (Box 35)
        - Minnesota, Circa 1993; audiocassette (Box 47)
        - Missouri, Circa 1995; audiocassette (Box 46)
        - Mississippi, 1995; audiocassette (Box 44)
        - New Haven (Connecticut), 1995; audiocassette (Box 42)
        - New York, Circa 1980s; audiocassette (Box 40)
        - North Carolina, Circa 1988- Circa 1995; 4 (Box 35, Box 39, Box 48–49)
        - North Dakota, Circa 1993; audiocassette (Box 47)
        - Pittsburgh (Pennsylvania), 1993 September; audiocassette (Box 35)
        - South Carolina, 1995; audiocassette (Box 43)
        - Southern Connecticut, 1993 September; audiocassette (Box 35)
        - Standard American, 1989; audiocassette (Box 36)
        - Tennessee, Circa 1995; 3 (Box 41, Box 43, Box 48)
        - Texas, 1989 April; audiocassette (Box 44)
        - Trinidad, 1995; audiocassette (Box 72)
        - Virginia, 1993 September; audiocassette (Box 35)
        - West Texas, Circa 1995; audiocassette (Box 46)
        - Western, Circa 1980s; audiocassette (Box 40)
    - Yugoslavia (Serbo-Croatia), 1991 Sep, 1992 December 8; 2 (Box 22, Box 51)
  - Draper, Ruth, The Italian Lesson, Doctors and Diets, No unitdate; audiocassette (Box 52)
  - Gister, Earle, "Brechtian Acting", 1988 March 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 104)
  - Grove, Eddy, Lecture on Michael Chekhov's contribution to actor training, 1987-1988; audiocassette (Box 53)
  - It's Not All Play, 1937; videotape (VHS) (Box 107)
    A silent film documenting the backstage preparations for a theatrical performance by Yale School of Drama.
  - Jack, Andrew, Lecture, "R.P. and England", 1988 October 10; audiocassette (Box 54–55)
  - Jamaica: Anansi stories and music, No unitdate; audiocassette (Box 56)
  - Katz, Leon, Lecture (DR36a), 1988 September 9; audiocassette (Box 57)
  - Play analysis, 1988 September 16-November 11; 4 (Box 58–61)
  - Pronunciation guides
    - Chekhov, Anton, Cherry Orchard, 1991; audiocassette (Box 62)
    - Chekhov, Anton, The Seagull, 1992; audiocassette (Box 63)
    - Chekhov, Anton, The Three Sisters, 1991 February; audiocassette (Box 64)
    - Chekhov, Anton, Wild Honey, 1995 January; audiocassette (Box 65)
    - Chekhov's Names, Circa 1988; audiocassette (Box 66)
    - Chekhov's Names and Uncle Vanya Names and Places in Depth, Circa 1989; audiocassette (Box 67)
    - Farquhar, George, The Beaux' Strategem, 1996; audiocassette (Box 68)
    - Friel, Brian, Translations, 1987 March; audiocassette (Box 69)
    - Fugard, Athol, My Children! My Africa!, 1991; audiocassette (Box 70)
      Words and names read by Athol Fugard.
      - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 70U)
    - Gorki, Maxim, Summerfolk, 1988 December 19; audiocassette (Box 71)
    - Ibsen, Henrik, Peer Gynt, 1994; audiocassette (Box 72)
    - Names from Ibsen's Plays, 1993 May 6; audiocassette (Box 73)
    - Matura, Mustapha, Playboy of the West Indies, 1989 April; audiocassette (Box 74)
    - Shakespeare, William, Henry IV Part I, 1993 December; audiocassette (Box 75)
    - Shakespeare, William, The Merchant of Venice, 1991 December 16; audiocassette (Box 76)
    - Shakespeare, William, Titus Andronicus, 1992 October 26; audiocassette (Box 77)
    - Names from August Strindberg's Plays, 1993 May; audiocassette (Box 78)
    - Vega, Lope de, Fuenteovejuna, Circa 1993; audiocassette (Box 79)
  - Safety Conference, Yale School of Drama: Fire Codes and Fire Safety, 1986 February 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 105)
  - Stories of Old Norwich, 1859-1920, No unitdate; audiocassette (Box 80)
  - Summerfolk
    - Session 2 with Anna Brodski, 1989 January 11; audiocassette (Box 81)
    - Music, Circa 1989; audiocassette (Box 82)
  - Turnabout: The Story of the Yale Puppeteers, commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1992 (Box 106)
  - Western Literature 226a, 1988 September 16-December 9; 8 (Box 83–90)
  - Wilder, Isabel, interview by Sara Low on experiences as member of Yale School Drama class of 1928, 1989 March 15; 2 (Box 91–92)
  - Winterfest seminars
    - Season IV. Dumang, Wasserstein, and Weaver, 1984 February 18; audiocassette (Box 93)
    - Season VI.
      - Tipton, Jennifer, Tharon Musser, and Ming Cho Lee (mod.), "Telling Stories Through Light", 1986 January 24; audiocassette (Box 94)
      - Morrison, Toni, August Wilson, and Robert Stepto (mod.), "The Poetry of Storytelling", 1986 January 25; audiocassette (Box 94)
        - Typed transcript (Box 116)
      - Simms, Laura, "A Concert of Wintertales," audiocassette, 1986 January 25 (Box 95)
      - Brever, Lee, Richard Foreman, and Gitta Honegger (mod.), "The Art of Storytelling", 1986 January 31; 2 (Box 95–96)